Hubbell Trading Post records, 1882-1968 (bulk 1905-1950)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Hubbell Trading Post records 1882-1968 (bulk 1905-1950)
AZ 375
Hubbell Trading Post
Hubbell Trading Post records pertain to vendor files, business materials, and personal and business correspondence.
252 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Historical Note
Located at Ganado, Arizona, on the Navajo Reservation; started by John Lorenzo Hubbell in 1876. It was later operated by family members; the last was his daughter-in-law Dorothy Smith Hubbell. She ran it as a museum until the National Park Service took responsibility for it as a National Historic Site, in 1967. Thirty-five other stores were established throughout the Southwest by John Lorenzo Hubbell and his family, and some of their records are included here. In addition to supplying the local Native Americans with needed goods, the Hubbell enterprise is significant for its promotion and national marketing of Navajo rugs and silverwork, as well as Hopi pottery and baskets.
Organization
This collection is organized into nine Sub-groups
Sub-group I: Correspondence, 1884-1968
Sub-group II: Vendor Files, 1890-1962
Sub-group III: Business Books & Records, 1882-1967
Sub-group IV: Legal Matters, 1882-1968
Sub-group V: Banking Matters, 1889-1966
Sub-group VI: Personal Materials, 1882-1968
Sub-group VII: Post Office Materials, 1885-1938
Sub-group VIII: Sales Books, 1912-1963
Sub-group IX: Advertisements, Price Lists, and Catalogs
Scope and Content Note
The bulk of this collection consists of vendor files, business materials, and correspondence. The correspondence series are comprised of incoming, outgoing, and Indian letters. Business correspondence includes government organizations, particularly the Republican party; Indian organizations, such as the Indian Arts and Crafts Board; and business organizations that bought Indian goods, notably Fred Harvey. Personal correspondence included that of artists and writers, such as Laura Adams Armer and Elbridge Ayer Burbank, employees, friends, local Navajo and Hopi individuals, and family members. Correspondence, as well as personal papers, are present for John Lorenzo Hubbell, his daughters Barbara H. Goodman and Adele H. Parker, his sons Roman Hubbell and Lorenzo Hubbell, Jr., and their spouses and children.
Off-post and intra-post vendor series contain the following: orders, invoices, consignment lists, freight bills, packing sips, statements of charges, receipts, loan notes, tax statements, rental notices, and credit memos. Long-term vendor relations are with the Babbitt Brothers Co., C.N. Cotton Co., and Gallup Mercantile.
The Business series are comprised of daily, summary, and Indian records; included are daybooks, cashbooks, individual accounts, and inventories. As with the intra-post vendor series, most of the Hubbell stores are represented, but Ganado, Winslow, and Oraibi have the most extensive records.
Legal items encompass maps, mortgages, titles, leases, estate and court records, and trading post licenses. Within the banking materials are statements, deposits, overdrafts, credits, World War II rationing accounts, and cancelled checks from numerous banks in Arizona, New Mexico, and California.
Other items in the collection are insurance company policies, post office records, sales books, and national store catalogs.
Hubbell, John Lorenzo -- Archives; Goodman, Barbara Hubbell; Parker, Adele Hubbell; Hubbell, Roman -- 1891-1957; Hubbell, Dorothy Smith; Hubbell, Lorenzo -- 1883-1943; Armer, Laura Adams -- 1874-1963 -- Correspondence; Burbank, E. A. (Elbridge Ayer) -- 1858-1949 -- Correspondence; United States -- Indian Arts and Crafts Board; Fred Harvey (Firm); Babbitt Brothers Trading Company; C.N. Cotton (Firm); Gallup Mercantile Company; Postal service -- Arizona -- History -- Sources; Trading posts; Navajo textile fabrics; Hopi Indians -- Trading posts; Hubbell Trading Post National Historic Site (Ganado, Ariz.) -- Archives; Southwest, New -- History -- 1848- -- Sources; Ganado (Ariz.) -- History -- Sources; Navajo Indian Reservation -- History -- Sources; Correspondence
Separated Material
Seventy boxes of sales slips were returned to the Hubbell Trading Post at Ganado, Arizona. Only a sample of the sales books have been processed. Seventy boxes of sales books are in storage.
Container List
- Sub-group I: Correspondence, 1884-1968
  Contains all correspondence not originating at a Hubbell-owned/operated trading post or store. Family members who were not immediate to J.L. Hubbell family members or who had no connection with a Hubbell-owned/operated trading post or store are also included here. Occasionally bills, sales slips, etc., when attached to the original letter, will be found here. Occasionally company form letters (even, though rarely, not specifically addressed to a Hubbell, Hubbell employee or Hubbell trading post) will be found here. Correspondence from a specific person may include such odds and ends as newspaper clippings about that person, notices or reviews of an author's books, notices of a painter's gallery shows, programs in which an individual takes part, articles or other writings, etc.; correspondence from a company may include advertising matter and other miscellaneous items.
  - Series I: Incoming Correspondence, 1884-1968
    - A--Alyea. (Box 1)
    - Amateur--Antrim. (Box 2)
    - Apache--Arizona Curio. (Box 3)
    - Arizona Disinfectant--Armstrong. (Box 4)
    - Arnett--Babbett & Roberts. (Box 5)
    - Battitt Brothers--Baird. (Box 6)
    - Bake--Barrye. (Box 7)
    - Barteldes--Bengler. (Box 8)
    - Ben-Hur--Bixby. (Box 9)
    - Black--Boston. (Box 10)
    - Botsford--Bronzynski. (Box 11)
    - Brooklyn--Burbank. (Box 12)
    - Burch--Byrne. (Box 13)
    - C--Candy. (Box 14)
      Cameron, Ralph file contains considerable material related to post offices. Cancelograph Co. file contains all materials related to this company and J.L. Hubbell's involvement with it (company stocks, corporate organization, announcement of stockholders' meetings, etc.).
    - Canfield--Cervantes. (Box 15)
    - Chaca--Clark. (Box 16)
    - Clarke--Coker. (Box 17)
    - Colbert--Cominsky. (Box 18)
    - Commercial--Cotton, C.N. Co. 1907 (Box 19)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1908-1913 (Box 20)
    - Cotton, CN., Co.--Crawford. 1914 (Box 21)
    - Creaghe--Dalton. (Box 22)
    - Damon--Dempster. (Box 23)
    - Dendahl--Doctor. (Box 24)
    - Dodd-Dunseath. (Box 25)
    - Duport--Ellrieux. (Box 26)
    - Elmer-Faye. (Box 27)
    - Featherstone--First National Bank, Albuquerque. 1918 (Box 28)
    - First National Bank, Albuquerque--Flitman. 1919 (Box 29)
    - Flores--Freer. (Box 30)
    - Freight--Galsh. (Box 31)
    - Gamble--Gignoux. (Box 32)
    - Gila--Government. (Box 33)
    - Grabbe--Gross. (Box 34)
    - Grossman--Hamley. (Box 35)
    - Hammacher--Harvey, Fred. 1905 (Box 36)
    - Harvey, Fred. 1906-1927 (Box 37)
    - Harvey, Fred--Hefter. 1928 (Box 38)
    - Hegler--Hillyer. (Box 39)
    - Hilton--Hostetter. (Box 40)
    - Hot-Hulsizer. (Box 41)
    - Humboldt--Indian Art. (Box 42)
    - Indian Arts--Indians. 1911 (Box 43)
      Contains all official correspondence from various Indian agencies and schools and all official correspondence from other governmental departments, bureaus, etc. which relates to Indians or Indian trading posts. Correspondence from the Navajo tribe--as distinct from federal tribal agencies--is found under that heading (box 62).
    - Indians. 1912-1933 (Box 44)
    - Indians--Inter-Tribal. 1934 (Box 45)
    - Ipp-Jordan. (Box 46)
    - Joseph-Kerr. (Box 47)
    - Kessler--Klumpp. (Box 48)
    - Knap--Krook. (Box 49)
    - Krueger--La Zear. (Box 50)
    - Leach--Liebeskind. (Box 51)
    - Life--Loring. (Box 52)
    - Los Angeles--Madinian. (Box 53)
    - Maestro--Marks. (Box 54)
    - Marleau--Maytag. (Box 55)
    - McAdams--McKinney. (Box 56)
    - McLaren--Mexizona. (Box 57)
    - Meyer--Mirobal. (Box 58)
    - Misbaugh--Mooney. (Box 59)
    - Moore--Murphy. (Box 60)
    - Murray--National Training. (Box 61)
    - National Union--Neustadter. (Box 62)
    - Neva--Noyes-Norman. (Box 63)
    - Nuanes--Osterkamp-Mead. (Box 64)
    - Otero--Parmelee-Dohrmann. (Box 65)
    - Parrish--Peshlakai. (Box 66)
    - Pete--Plywood. (Box 67)
    - Pockels--Purity. (Box 68)
    - Putcamp--Renshaw. (Box 69)
    - Reo-Riordan. (Box 70)
      Contains official correspondence from all county, state, and national Republican Party organizations; includes most correspondence of J.L. Hubbell as chairman of the Arizona Central Committee (but not his personal/business correspondence; this will be found in the next series).
    - Ripon--Routt. (Box 71)
    - Rowe--San Gabriel. (Box 72)
    - San Jacinto--Schmitz. (Box 73)
    - Schnoor--Shattuck-George. (Box 74)
    - Sheaffer--Skylight. (Box 75)
    - Slade--Southwest Society. (Box 76)
    - Southwest Trade--Stapley. (Box 77)
    - Star--Sumner. (Box 78)
    - Sun--Texas. (Box 79)
    - Thackara--Trekell. (Box 80)
    - Tribble--United Press. (Box 81)
    - United States--United Workingmen's. (Box 82)
    - Universal--Vorys. (Box 83)
    - Voss--Waxler. (Box 84)
    - Weafer--Wetzler. (Box 85)
    - Whalen's--Wilkinson. (Box 86)
    - Will--Wister. (Box 87)
    - Ysisarri--Zwebell. (Box 89)
    - Telegrams, copies of originals. September 4, 1944-June 27, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Telegrams, copies of originals. July 5, 1945-September 5, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Telegrams, copies of originals. September 28, 1945-October 26, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified correspondents. 1890-1929 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified correspondents. 1930-1957 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified correspondents. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Hubbell Papers: correspondence between Dorothy S. Hubbell, Park Service officials and University of Arizona personnel concerning the University's becoming a repository for the Papers. (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Series II: Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence, 1884-1968
    Contains all business correspondence of the Hubbell-owned/operated trading posts or stores. Contains the personal correspondence of the immediate members of the J.L. Hubbell family: Barbara H. Goodman, Adele H. Goodman, Roman Hubbell, and Lorenzo Hubbell, Jr., and their wives/husbands and children. Also contains personal correspondence for all others (both family and non-family) who worked for the Hubbells. Many persons will be found both in this and in the previous series.
    - "Cotton Leather Book," parts 1-8, pp. 2-390. September 1884-April 1886 (Box 91, Folder 1-8)
    - "Cotton Leather Book," parts 9-15, pp. 391-754. May 1886-January 1888 (Box 92, Folder 1-7)
    - "Cotton Leather Book," parts 16-21, pp. 755-1025. February 1888-January 1889 (Box 93, Folder 1-6)
    - Letter book: pp.1-656 (signed by J.L. Hubbell) and pp. 657-700 (signed by J.L. Hubbell per F.M. Parker). 1901-1904, 1914 (Box 94)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. 1878-April 1909 (Box 95)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. May 1909-February 1912 (Box 96)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. March 1912-February 1913 (Box 97)
    - Letter book: signed mostly by Lorenzo Hubbell, Jr., some by F.M. Parker. 1913-1914 (Box 98)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. March 1913-1915 (Box 99)
    - Letter book: pp.1-160 (signed by J.L. Hubbell per F.M. Parker) and pp. 161 (handwritten letter signed by JLH). 1914-1915 (Box 100)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. 1916-1919 (Box 101)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. 1920-October 1923 (Box 102)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. November 1923-April 1925 (Box 103)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. May 1925-August 1926 (Box 104)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. September 1926-April 1928 (Box 105)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. May 1928-October 1931 (Box 106)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. November 1931-April 1933 (Box 107)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. May 1933-March 1935 (Box 108)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. April 1935-July 1936 (Box 109)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. August 1936-September 1938 (Box 110)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. October 1938-1939 (Box 111)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. 1940 (Box 112)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. 1941 (Box 113)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. 1942-July 1943 (Box 114)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. August 1943-September 1944 (Box 115)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. October 1944-March 1946 (Box 116)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. April 1946-March 1947 (Box 117)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. April 1947-February 1948 (Box 118)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. March 1948-April 1949 (Box 119)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. May 1949-September 1950 (Box 120)
    - Outgoing/Intra-post Correspondence. October 1950-1968 (Box 121)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from J.L. Hubbell to family, employees, and others. (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from Lorenzo, Jr., to family and employees (Armijo--J.L. Hubbell). (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from Lorenzo, Jr., to family and employees (Roman Hubbell--Wesson). (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from Lorenzo, Jr., to family and employees (to all others: A-M). (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from Lorenzo, Jr., to family and employees (to all others: N-Unknown). (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from Roman and Dorothy S. Hubbell to family, employees, and others. (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from Fletcher Corrigan to L.H., Jr., and others. (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from H.C. Hibben to L.H., Jr., and others. (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from Jim c. Karigan to JLH, RH, Forrest Parker and others. (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from others family and employees (Antonio Armijo--Emerson Horace). (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from other family and employees (Charles Hubbell--Thomas S. Hubbell). (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from other family and employees (Earl W. Johnson--Bernaard Papke). (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from other family and employees (Forest M. & Adele H. Parker--Myrtle Poe). (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Undated/Incomplete Correspondence: from other family and employees (Andy Romero--unidentified employees). (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Series III: Indian Letters, 1884-1968
    Contains correspondence, mostly from local (Navajo or Hopi) individuals, addresses directly to a Hubbell or Hubbell employee, or addressed to a family member or the correspondent but sent to a Hubbell or Hubbell employee to be read to that family member. Indians who operated their own trading posts or other business will not be found here. Indians who worked in a Hubbell trading post or store will not be found here. For any given individual, all three series should be consulted.
    - Indian Letters: A-S. (Box 124, Folder 1-10)
    - Indian Letters: T-unidentified correspondents. (Box 125, Folder 1-4)
- Sub-group II: Vendor Files, 1890-1962
  This group is concerned with the exchange of goods or services between the Hubbells and individuals or companies or with the exchange of goods and services within the Hubbell business. Within this group will be found such things as orders, invoices, consignment lists, freight bills, packing slips, statements of charges, receipts, notes (loans), tax assessments/statements, rental notices, etc.
  - Series I: Off-Post Vendors, 1890-1962
    Contains all orders, invoices, freight bills, statements, etc. between an individual or company and the Hubbell business. The flow of goods or services may be in either direction or both; ie. an order by the Hubbells for goods or services from a person or company, or an order by a person or company for goods or services from the Hubbells, or a combination of the two. The transaction will be under the name of the individual or company, whether customer or supplier (vendor), in an alphabetical sequence.
    - A--Alcoholic. (Box 126)
    - Alden--Antony. (Box 127)
    - Apache--Arizona Industrial Commission. (Box 128)
    - Arizona Land Department--Arizona Janitor. (Box 129)
    - Arizona Lumber--Arizona Republic. (Box 130)
    - Arizona Saddlery--Armour. (Box 131)
    - Armstron--Babbitt Brothers. 1918 (Box 132)
    - Babbitt Brothers. 1919-1923 (Box 133)
    - Babbitt Brothers. 1924-1937 (Box 134)
    - Babbitt Brothers. 1938-1943 (Box 135)
    - Babbitt Brothers. 1944-1946 (Box 136)
    - Babbitt Brothers. 1947-1948 (Box 137)
    - Babbitt Brothers. 1949-1950 (Box 138)
    - Babbitt Brothers--Bacon. 1951 (Box 139)
    - Badger--Barton. (Box 140)
    - Bashford--Beverly. (Box 141)
    - Bickel--Bowser. (Box 142)
    - Box--Bryan. (Box 143)
    - Bubany--Butler. (Box 144)
    - Butler Brothers--Calumet. (Box 145)
    - Cambridge--Cheyenne. (Box 146)
    - Chicago--Coca-Cola. (Box 147)
    - Cochise--Commonwealth. (Box 148)
    - Compton's--Cotton, C.N., Co. 1900 (Box 149)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1901-1905 (Box 150)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1906-1907 (Box 151)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1908-1909 (Box 152)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1910 (Box 153)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1911 (Box 154)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1912 (Box 155)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1913 (Box 156)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1914 (Box 157)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1915 (Box 158)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1916 (Box 159)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1917-1920 (Box 160)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co. 1921-1925 (Box 161)
    - Cotton, C.N., Co.--Crawley's. 1926 (Box 162)
    - Credit--Davies. (Box 163)
    - Davis--de Young. (Box 164)
    - Diamond--Edge. (Box 165)
    - Effron--Epstein. (Box 166)
    - Escalada--First Austrian. (Box 167)
    - First National--Ford. (Box 168)
    - Fore--Gallup Automobile. (Box 169)
    - Gallup Cadillac--Gallup Mercantile. 1931 (Box 170)
    - Gallup Mercantile. 1932-1953 (Box 171)
    - Gallup Mercantile. 1954-1956 (Box 172)
    - Gallup mercantile--Gamble. 1957 (Box 173)
    - Ganem--Gentry. (Box 174)
    - Gerevitz--Government. (Box 175)
    - Grace--Gretsch. (Box 176)
    - Griffin--Gross, Kelly. 1937 (Box 177)
    - Gross, Kelly. 1938-1947 (Box 178)
    - Gross, Kelly--Halstead. 1948 (Box 179)
    - Hambaugh--Hartman. (Box 180)
    - Harvey--Hayward. (Box 181)
    - Heard--Hirsch. (Box 182)
    - Hobert--Hudson. (Box 183)
    - Huff's--Ilfeld-Spitz. (Box 184)
    - Illinois--Industrial. (Box 185)
      Indian file contains all reservation agency business dealings with the Hubbells. It is divided into Hopi, Navajo, and other Indians.
    - Ingham's--Johnston. (Box 186)
    - Jolly--K & B Company. 1960 (Box 187)
    - K & B Company--Kemska. 1961 (Box 188)
    - Kendrick--Kimbell-Gallup Co. 1962 (Box 189)
    - Kimbell-Gallup Co.--Kirk Brothers. 1963,1929 (Box 190)
    - Kirk Brothers--Kley. 1930 (Box 191)
    - Kline--Korricks. (Box 192)
    - Krafft--Lederman. (Box 193)
    - Lee--Lily. (Box 194)
    - Linda--Loyal. (Box 195)
    - Lubbert--Manhouse. (Box 196)
    - Manitou--Matson. (Box 197)
    - Maupin--McKinley. (Box 198)
    - McLaughlin--Mid-west. (Box 199)
    - Milan's--Mlocker. (Box 200)
    - Mockelford--Momsen Dunnegan Ryan. 1947- (Box 201)
    - Momsen Dunnegan Ryan--Morgan's. 1948 (Box 202)
    - Morrell--Museum. (Box 203)
    - Myer--National. (Box 204)
    - Nava-Hopi--Navajo County. (Box 205)
    - Navajo Curio--Norick. (Box 206)
    - North--Northern Arizona Gas. (Box 207)
    - Northern Arizona Light--Olds Brothers Lumber. 1946 (Box 208)
    - Olds Brothers Lumber--Packard. 1947 (Box 209)
    - Padgett--Patch and Marley. 1946 (Box 210)
    - Patch and Marley--Pendleton. 1947 (Box 211)
    - Penney--Pepsi-Cola. 1959 (Box 212)
    - Pepsi-Cola--Peyton. 1950 (Box 213)
    - Phelon--Pray. (Box 214)
    - Precht--Rainbow. (Box 215)
    - Raleigh--Redlich. (Box 216)
    - Reed--Richter. (Box 217)
    - Ricketts--Ruth. (Box 218)
    - S--Schafer. (Box 219)
    - Scheer--Scrivner. (Box 220)
    - Sealy--Shelton's. (Box 221)
    - Sheppe--Smithy's. (Box 222)
    - Smogeski--Southwest News. (Box 223)
    - Southwest sales--Stampley. (Box 224)
    - Standard--Standard Oil. 1940 (Box 225)
    - Standard Oil. 1941-1949 (Box 226)
    - Standard Oil--Stinson. 1950 (Box 227)
    - Stocker--Tall. (Box 228)
    - Tammen--Texas Bitulithic. (Box 229)
    - Texas Candy--Tovrea. (Box 230)
    - Town--United States Manufacturers. (Box 231)
    - United States Army--Internal Revenue Service. (Box 232)
    - United States Land Office--Valley Gold. 1961 (Box 233)
    - Valley Gold--Vogel, O.A. 1962, 1909 (Box 234)
    - Vogel, O.A.--Wax. 1910 (Box 235)
    - Wayland's--Western. (Box 236)
    - Wetherill--Wilshire. (Box 237)
    - Wilson--Winslow Quality Bakery. 1947 (Box 238)
    - Winslow Quality Bakery--Worth. 1948 (Box 239)
    - Wright--Zuni. (Box 240)
  - Series II: Intra-Post Vendors, 1890-1962
    Contains all orders, charges, credit memos, statements, wholesale/retail invoices, etc. concerned with the exchange of goods between one Hubbell post/store and another. The arrangement is alphabetical by post of origin; ie. if an order is from Pinon to Winslow it would be filed under Pinon but the statement of charges is from Winslow and would be found under Winslow.
    - Big Mountain. 1940, 1945-1947 (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Black Mountain. 1914-1918,1921-1925, 1931, 1934-1937 (Box 241, Folder 2-4)
    - Blue Canyon. 1927 (Box 241, Folder 5)
    - Cedar Springs. 1908-1915 (Box 241, Folder 6-8)
    - Chinle. 1890, 1913-1918 (Box 242, Folder 1-4)
    - Cornfields. 1905-1908 (Box 242, Folder 5-7)
    - Cornfields. 1909-1918 (Box 243, Folder 1-9)
    - Cow Springs. 1935, no date (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Dam Store. 1913-1919 (Box 244, Folder 2-8)
    - Dam Store. 1920 (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Farmington Farm. 1914 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Gallup. 1908-August1915 (Box 245, Folder 3-7)
    - Gallup. September 1915-October 1916 (Box 246, Folder 1-7)
    - Gallup. November 1916-1917 (Box 247, Folder 1-6)
    - Gallup. 1918-1921, 1926-1929, 1931-1933, 1936-1938, 1942-1943 (Box 248, Folder 1-3)
    - Ganado: intra-post/off-post sales/purchases and parts 1-3. December 31, 1906-July 12, 1902; December 21, 1906-October 2, 1905 (Box 248, Folder 4-6)
    - Ganado: parts 4-7. September 29, 1905-July 12, 1902 (Box 249, Folder 1-4)
    - Ganado. November-December 1905, 1907-1911 (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: intra-post/off-post sales/purchases part 1. April 30, 1919-April 5, 1918 (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - Ganado: parts 2-7. March 3, 1919-August 1, 1916 (Box 250, Folder 1-6)
    - Ganado: parts 8-12. July 31, 1916-August 2, 1915 (Box 251, Folder 1-5)
    - Ganado: parts 13-17. July 30, 1915-March 2, 1914 (Box 252, Folder 1-5)
    - Ganado: parts 18-23. February 18, 1914-January 1, 1912 (Box 253, Folder 1-6)
    - Ganado: parts 24-26. December 28, 1911-January 1, 1911 (Box 254, Folder 1-3)
    - Ganado. February 1912-1914 (Box 254, Folder 4-8)
    - Ganado. 1915-August 1917 (Box 255, Folder 1-9)
    - Ganado. September 1917-1919, 1921-1923, 1926, 1928-1943, 1952 (Box 256, Folder 1-4)
    - Greasewood. 1928, 1924-1936 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Hollywood. 1926-1928 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Hub store. 1934 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Lorenzo Hubbell Motor Company. 1946-1951 (Box 256, Folder 8-12)
    - L.H. Motor Co. 1952 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Hubbell Service Station, Winslow. 1937-1939 (Box 257, Folder 2)